wisebread.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy

You are not authorized to post comments.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

This Privacy Policy was developed by [Killer Aces Media](http://killeraces.com/), LLC (“Killer Aces” “we” or “our”) as an extension of our commitment to combine quality content, products, and services with integrity in dealing with our users. This Privacy Policy covers all of Killer Aces's websites (“KA Websites”), including the one you are currently visiting (“Website”), and any associated content including RSS feeds, emails, newsletters, forums, podcasts, user comments, and social applications.

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using KA Websites and our products and services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Please also read our User Agreement and Website Submission Rules . Your use of KA Websites constitutes agreement to the User Agreement, Website Submission Rules, and this Privacy Policy.

**Children Under 13 Years of Age**

No person under 13 should disclose any information on KA Websites. KA Websites are not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. You may learn more about protecting children’s privacy online by visiting [www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy).

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit KA Websites you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and usage information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse KA Websites (“Passive Information”).

**Active Information You Choose to Provide**

We may receive and store any information you choose to enter on KA Websites or provide to us in any other way (such as email, regular mail, IM, or telephone contact). KA Websites generally collect personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For example, when you register for a user account, subscribe to our publication, make a purchase, create a user profile, enter a contest, complete a survey, sign up for a newsletter, use our forums, leave a comment, or register for any of our services, you will be asked to provide information such as your name, email address, address, or phone number. Other optional demographic information such as your age, gender, or educational level may also be requested.

If you provide personally identifiable information, it will be used to provide you with the service you have requested. For example:

  * Register for an account: We require a user name and a working email address.

  * Participate in a contest: We require your real name, verification of information to satisfy legal requirements and the conditions of the contest, and information required to notify you and ship prizes to you if you win (such information may include name, email, telephone number, and a shipping address).

  * Participating in a survey: We may ask you to provide relevant data regarding your preferences and demographics information to answer survey questions.

  * Creating a user profile: You can put as much or as little biographical information in your profile. You can add information such as a bio, personal preferences, contact information, photograph, etc.

**Passive Information Collected**

KA Websites utilize standard technologies called “cookies” and "log files" to collect information about how KA Websites are used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at KA Websites, the websites visited just before and just after KA Websites, what type of web browser (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, Firefox, etc.) you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit “cookie” information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the “Help” section of your browser to correctly do so.

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s web browser on one website to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from website to website and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

**How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other products or services we think may be of interest to our users. If you provided personally identifiable information in order to receive a specific service or product, it will be used to provide you with the service or product you have requested.

We may use the Active Information or Passive Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our Website, new services, forgotten passwords, contest winnings, changes to our agreements and policies, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an email at:

We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance and design our Website to make it easier, faster, and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our Website, when they visit and how they use our service. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address. However, Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits for your viewing on KA Websites.

**Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To**

You may be able to access third party websites through KA Websites. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those websites’ privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such websites. When you choose to shop at such websites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.

**Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties**

We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics, and user patterns based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers or service providers.

In the course of serving advertisements on KA Websites, our third-party advertisers may place or identify a unique cookie on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information. This information may include your IP address, ISP, the browser you used to visit KA Websites, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is often used for geotargeting purposes (showing Los Angeles restaurant ads to someone in Los Angeles, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing personal finance ads to someone who frequents personal finance sites).

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/ "behavioral ads opt out").

**Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law**

We may be required by law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us.

**How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?**

We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information and Passive Information. Your postings on this Website and other communications you may have with us via email or regular mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.

**How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information About Products or Services By Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information**

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please send us an email at:

We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this Website as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use KA Websites.
